Welcome to The Unit.
Fun facts about ecosystems. B.
Kitty and David are talking about ecosystems.
Work in pairs and discuss the topic.
Use the conversation below as a model.
Know anything about ecosystems, David?
I know that grasslands in different places are home to different animals.
In Inner Mongolia, there are horses and cows, but in Africa there are lions and giraffes. Oh really?
Do you know anything about deserts?
Well, it's very dry in deserts, because there's little rain.
And the difference in temperature between day and night is huge.
Yes, the climate in deserts is so awful that only a few animals and plants can live there. It's true.
The desert plants keep water in their leaves and many animals there get water from these plants.